In our darkest hour, a hero will rise.
Wolf Hound is a war, action film directed by Michael B. Chait.
Inspired by the real-life German special operations unit KG 200 that shot down, repaired, and flew Allied aircraft as Trojan horses, "Wolf Hound"
takes place in 1944 German-occupied France and follows the daring exploits of Jewish-American fighter pilot Captain David Holden.
Ambushed behind enemy lines, Holden must rescue a captured B-17 Flying Fortress crew, evade a ruthless enemy
stalking him at every turn, and foil a plot that could completely alter the outcome of World War II.
Captain David Holden, played by James Maslow.
Major Erich Roth, played by Trevor Donovan.
Colonel Krieger, played by John Turk.
Captain Rolf Werner, played by Michael Wayne Foster.
Captain Heinrich Roth, played by Ronald Woodhead.
Captain Richard Thompson, played by Michael Parrish.
Huckleberry "Huck" Hound is a fictional cartoon character, a
blue dog who speaks with a North Carolina accent.
He first appeared in the series The Huckleberry Hound Show.
The cartoon was one of six TV shows to win an Emmy Award in 1960 as a Primetime Emmy Award for
Outstanding Children's Program; the first animated series to receive such an award.
In most of his cartoons he has different jobs, with results that backfire, yet
usually coming out on top, either through slow persistence or sheer luck.
He has been a Roman gladiator, a medieval knight, a
dogcatcher, a policeman and a rocket scientist.
He also appears in futuristic cartoons, as an intergalactic space
policeman, alongside other Hanna-Barbera characters.
His off-key and inaccurate rendition of "Oh My Darling,
Clementine" was often used as a running gag.